Curriculum VITAE

PERSONAL DATA

NAME: KANINGINI
MIDDLE NAME: LUTALA
FIRST NAME: NETHO Junior

ADDRESS: Route Joal 2 Km, Mbour, Thies, Sénégal

PHONE: +221 785963525

EMAIL: netho.j.k.lutala@aims-senegal.org

SUMMARY

I am a master's student specializing in Computer Security. I hold a bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering. I have knowledge in human resource management, project management and administration, management public. I am able to adapt to a new environment and I have analytical and problem solving skills.

EXPERIENCE

SEPTEMBER 2015-SEPT 2019	National president of Youth Popular Podium, (PPJ-DRC)
	PPJ is a platform for young people with several objectives in different fields including education, the environment, agriculture, new information technology, etc. I coordinated all activities done by the organization.
Juin 2017-August 2019	Assistant at University of Kinshasa, DRC My tasks included:
	Computer Security, Operating System, Computer Network, Computer Architecture, Architecture of Teleinformatic Systems, Operating System Design.
SEPT 2016-MARCH 2017	Trainee at the IT Department of the Ministry of Finance /KINSHASA

(DRC) with the task of managing the payroll application.

EDUCATION

SEPTEMBER 2019	Masters Student specializing in Computer Security, at African Institute for Mathematical Sciences (AIMS), Senegal.
July 2017	Bachelor's degree in Mathematics and Computer Science, University of Kinshasa, Major : Computer Engineering, DRC.
JULY 2015	Graduate diploma in SCIENCE, University of Kinshasa, Major : Computer Engineering, DRC.
JULY 2010	State diploma in MATH-PHYSICS, Kalumbwa Institute, DRC.

CERTIFICATES

Certified in the Building a Google Firebase Web Application JULY 2020: https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/records/SQM9WZARVJC8 Certified in the Introduction to the Internet of Things and Embedded Systems JULY 2020 : https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/records/2YDZU6GXFNYU JULY 2020: Certified in the Usable Security https://coursera.org/share/41dc34a1179330f0a7fd7978e4adfd03 Certified in Google Cloud Platform Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure JUN 2020 : https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/records/WQ8PZ5UV6Y5Y Certified in the Blockchain and Cryptocurrency Explained MAY 2020: https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/X7VSBSWKCQVG Certified in the Industrial IoT on Google Cloud Platform MAY 2020: https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/records/HS6GPK3SSTFX Certified in Blockchain: Foundations and Use Cases APRIL. 2020: https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/XSD6BZ83SDE3 Certified in Build the Voting Application using Blockchain APRIL. 2020: https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/8a217c50-c80a-40f5-a849-5dbad598dbd6 APRIL. 2020: Certified in Cyber Threats and Attack Vectors https://coursera.org/share/aaf583cbe3a41e67331714967dde1808 Certified in Python /IBM APRIL. 2020: https://www.youracclaim.com/earner/earned/badge/3306ea2f-ad14-4c7b-a532-649bb6c45284 Certified in Enterprise System Management and Security APRIL. 2020: hhttps://coursera.org/share/2052dda1c6c143dbadc6b7a7e05eb27c Certified in Build your Voting Application using Blockchain APRIL. 2020: https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/8a217c50-c80a-40f5-a849-5dbad598dbd6 Certified in Identify and Investigate Cybersecurity Threats /IBM MARCH. 2020 : https://www.vouracclaim.com/earner/earned/badge/dfb987db-5eab-4ce5-815d-0d8ea0194748 FEB. 2020: Certified in Cloud Computing /IBM https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/8a8d3938-98d0-4e25-9174-57a5095d377a Certified in Cyber Security /IBM FEB. 2020: https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/61a63344-363d-4569-b6b9-690fb69edc9f

FEB. 2020: Certified in Internet of Things (IoT) /IBM

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/2df796b2-59f7-4eec-8961-d538d435b6fd

JAN. 2020: Certified in Blockchain Intro /IBM

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/cd9ea651-41e0-4605-bae7-9ad1faf038ac

MAY. 2018: Certified in Linux System Administration

Ref: Campus Numérique Fraconcophone(DRC/KINSHASA)

FEB. 2018: Certified in Linux Network administration

Ref: Campus Numérique Fraconcophone(DRC/KINSHASA)

MARCH 2016: Interface-Homme-Machine (IHM)

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH: Good
FRENCH: Very good
LINGALA: Very good
SWAHILI: Mother tongue

COMPUTER SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES: Python, Java, C(C-sharp), Visual Basic, PHP, Html;

VIRTUAL ENVIRONMENT: Interpreting skills in environment such as proteus and

VIRTUALIZATION WITH ORACLE VM, VIRTUALBOX AND VMWARE;

DATABASE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM: SQL Server, Mysql, Mongo DB, Access;

MODELING DATA: UML and MERISE;

DATA ANALYSIS: Pandas, NumPy, ElasticSearch, Kibana, Octave;

DATA COLLECTION: Web scraping;

PROJECT MANAGEMENT: GitHub, BitBucket;

OPERATING SYSTEM: Linux and Windows System Administration;

NETWORK: Linux and Window Administration Network;

OFFICE SOFTWARE: Microsoft Office, LibreOffice:

LANGUAGE FOR EDITING SCIENTIFIC TEXT: Latex.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Machine learning, Deep learning, Operational research, NodeJs, Node-Red, React, IBM Cloud.

INTERESTS AND ACTIVITIES

Technology, Open-Source, Programming; Paradoxes in Decision Making, Behavioural Finance, Football, Travelling

REFFERENCES

Professor Franck Kalala Mutombo

Academic Manager of AIMS Senegal franckm@aims-senegal.org Position:

EMAIL:

Professor Pierre Kasengedia Motumbe General Manager of ISTA KINSHASA kasengedia@ista.ac.cd

Position:

EMAIL: